1. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Page_Book London Theater Tickets  Get Exclusive Deals  Offers/input_SearchBar"), 30)
7. Search for The Simon and Garfunkel Story
11. sendKeys(findTestObject("Page_Book London Theater Tickets  Get Exclusive Deals  Offers/input_SearchBar"), Keys.chord(ENTER))
15. delay(2)
19. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Page_Book London Theater Tickets  Get Exclusive Deals  Offers/h1_The Simon and Garfunkel Story"), 30)
23. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Page_Book London Theater Tickets  Get Exclusive Deals  Offers/div_Book Now"), 30)
27. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("Page_Book London Theater Tickets  Get Exclusive Deals  Offers/div_Book Now"), 30)
31. click(findTestObject("Page_Book London Theater Tickets  Get Exclusive Deals  Offers/div_Book Now"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
35. switchToWindowIndex(1)
39. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Page_The Simon and Garfunkel Story London  Best Prices on West End Tickets/div_DateSelection"), 30)
43. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Page_The Simon and Garfunkel Story London  Best Prices on West End Tickets/div_DateSelection"), 30)
49. Pick a date
53. delay(3)
57. waitForElementNotPresent(findTestObject("Page_The Simon and Garfunkel Story London  Best Prices on West End Tickets/div_SpinningLoader"), 30)
61. switchToFrame(findTestObject("Page_The Simon and Garfunkel Story London  Best Prices on West End Tickets/iframe_seatBooking"), 30)
67. Pick a seat
71. switchToDefaultContent()
75. delay(3)
79. click(findTestObject("Page_The Simon and Garfunkel Story London  Best Prices on West End Tickets/span_SeatSelectionNextButton"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
85. Fill form details ( CC details are junk )
89. setText(findTestObject("Page_The Simon and Garfunkel Story London  Best Prices on West End Tickets/input_First Name"), FirstName)
93. setText(findTestObject("Page_The Simon and Garfunkel Story London  Best Prices on West End Tickets/input_Last Name"), LastName)
97. setText(findTestObject("Page_The Simon and Garfunkel Story London  Best Prices on West End Tickets/input_Email"), Email)
101. setText(findTestObject("Page_The Simon and Garfunkel Story London  Best Prices on West End Tickets/input_Confirm Email"), Email)
105. setText(findTestObject("Page_The Simon and Garfunkel Story London  Best Prices on West End Tickets/input_Phone"), PhoneNumber)
109. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Page_The Simon and Garfunkel Story London  Best Prices on West End Tickets/input_Card Number"), 10)
113. setText(findTestObject("Page_The Simon and Garfunkel Story London  Best Prices on West End Tickets/input_Card Number"), CCNumber)
117. setText(findTestObject("Page_The Simon and Garfunkel Story London  Best Prices on West End Tickets/input_Card Number_Expiry (MMYY)"), CCExpiry)
121. setText(findTestObject("Page_The Simon and Garfunkel Story London  Best Prices on West End Tickets/input_CVV"), CVV)
125. setText(findTestObject("Page_The Simon and Garfunkel Story London  Best Prices on West End Tickets/input_Card Holder Name"), CardHolderName)
129. delay(2)
135. Click on next
139. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Page_The Simon and Garfunkel Story London  Best Prices on West End Tickets/span_Invalid card details"), 30)
143. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Page_The Simon and Garfunkel Story London  Best Prices on West End Tickets/span_Invalid card details"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
147. closeWindowIndex(1)
151. switchToWindowIndex(0)
155. delay(1)